Enter the library window, double-click on the Avid file, find the FemaleVR folder, double-click on the FVR Feifei file, and drag it into the 3D window.
In the library window, find the Practice Files file, double-click on the B-Basic file, find the C-Tissue file, double-click on the Shoot file, or drag it into the 3D window.
Click OK to import the DXF file.
Use the adjustment panel tool.
On the 2D grid, single-click and drag the mouse to select the Shoukofu and Shouchatiao versions.
Make sure all the versions are selected.
Place the selected version next to the Shou.
Also select the Fanling and LiLing versions of the shirt, and place them next to the DaShengBeibu version.
Use the adjustment panel tool to place the versions together.
In the 2D window, arrange the T-shirt version around the virtual model shadow.
Only half of the clothing versions are provided.
You need to duplicate the other half.
Use the adjustment panel tool.
Right-click on the back, and select the Edit Folder line in the menu.
Open the back page.
Use the adjustment panel tool.
Select the back page from the 2D window, except for the collar.
Right-click on the panel.
Select the Column-linked version, the symmetrical version, the version and the sewing line.
Press Shift, and place the copied version level to the other side.
In the 3D window, select Rearrange 2D Arrangement Position.
All.
Connect the 2D window to the 3D window.
Select the mouse in the 4th in the 3D vertical tool bar.
Single-click to display the arrangement point.
Open the arrangement point of the virtual model.
Some arrangement points have been blocked.
Use the adjustment panel tool in the 2D window.
Select all the panels.
Press Ctrl-J to select all the panels.
Move the panel.
Select the arrangement point that has been blocked.
There are layers on both sides of the front panel.
Left-click on the right front panel.
Select the positional ball.
Use the pull of the positional ball.
Arrange the right front panel to the upper left front panel.
Rotate the view to see the gap between the panels.
Left-click on the sleeve.
Use the positional ball tool.
Arrange the sleeve panel to the sleeve.
Rotate it to see the gap between the panels.
At the 3D window, press the left button on the arrangement point and put the panel down.
At the 2D window, press Shift and select the sleeve panel and the sleeve fork panel.
At the 3D window, put the panel on the arrangement point of the arm.
Press the shortcut key 8 and rotate the view to the rear view.
At the 2D window, use the adjustment panel tool, press Shift and select the back preview and the back panel at the same time.
At the 3D window, press the back view and put the panel down.
At the 3D window, put the panel on the arrangement point of the back view.
At the 3D window, put the panel on the arrangement point of the wrist.
Press the shortcut key 2 and rotate the view to the front view.
At the 3D window, select the mouse and select the fourth in the 3D vertical tool bar.
Select the display arrangement point and hide the model arrangement point.
At the 2D window,
use the line alignment tool to align the front and rear.
Pay attention to the alignment direction when aligning.
At the 2D window, align the sleeve and the arm.
Pay attention to the alignment direction.
When the pointy line is cut, use the n-line alignment tool.
First select the sleeve line.
Press the Shift key and select the arm on the arm.
After aligning, release Shift.
Continue to use the line alignment tool.
Select the blue base line and right-click to select Cut from the menu.
The selected inner line number will be cut off on the embroidery board.
Select and drag the new outline line of the cut-off tool to adjust its length.
Use the Undo Shift tool to select the blue base line that represents the embroidered bar.
Press the Return key on the keyboard to hook the base line to the inner line.
Use the Line Embroidery tool to sew the embroidered bar to the sleeve bar.
When sewing, be careful that the embroidered bar needs to be open on one side,
and do not sew the part of the embroidered bar to the sleeve.
Use the Collar Expansion tool to create the inner line.
Select the two blue base lines that are the farthest from the embroidered bar.
Press the Return key on the keyboard to convert the base line to the inner line.
In the 2D window, select the Embroidered Bar Tool.
First, select the inner line that is the farthest from the embroidered bar.
In the attribute editor, change the fold angle of the inner line to 0.
Change the fold angle of the other inner line to 0.
Change the fold angle of the other inner line to 360 degrees.
Use the Line Embroidery tool to do relative embroidery on both sides of the 360-degree line.
Use the Free Embroidery tool to do relative embroidery on both ends of the 0-degree line.
Use the Embroidery tool to select the embroidered line on the sleeve bar.
In the attribute editor, change the type of embroidered line to Turned.
After activating the simulation, the fold will be more even.
Use the Free Embroidery tool to divide the bottom of the sleeve bar strip and the bottom of the sleeve.
While embroidering, it is necessary to keep the side open.
Do not merge the part of the sleeve bar strip with the sleeve.
In the attribute editor, change the type of embroidered line to Turned.
After activating the simulation, the fold will be more even.
Use the Free Embroidery tool to merge the sleeve bar strip onto the sleeve.
Use the Free Embroidery tool to create an embroidered line on the sleeve bar strip.
Start from the right side and move to the left side.
After finishing the first half of the sewing, sew the second half of the sewing and press Shift to create a sewing line on the sleeve strip.
Then continue to sew on the sleeve strip.
Because the fold is folded, there is no need to sew.
When sewing, pay attention to keep the direction of the sewing line consistent to avoid twisting.
In the 3D tool bar, select the twist tool.
In the 2D tool bar, there is a blue basic line mark on the panel, indicating the position of the button or buttonhole.
On the panel, press once to indicate that the buttonhole line will appear on the 2D panel.
And at the same time, the buttonhole image will appear in 3D.
In the 3D tool bar, select the move buttonhole tool.
In the 2D window, press to select the buttonhole created.
Right-click on the button, select copy from the pop-up menu.
Right-click to select paste from the blank.
In the second window,
on the basic line, left-click to create a new buttonhole.
Use the move buttonhole tool.
Right-click on the second buttonhole in the 2D window.
Right-click to select copy from the pop-up menu.
Right-click to select paste from the blank.
Press the Shift key and drag the mouse to move the buttonhole on the vertical line.
Place the mouse on the third basic line.
Right-click to select the dialogue window.
Enter the number of buttons.
Click OK to create a buttonhole.
In the 3D window buttonhole tool, press to select the buttonhole tool.
In the 2D window, there is a blue basic line mark on the panel,
indicating the location of the buttonhole or buttonhole installation.
On the panel, click here to indicate that the buttonhole line will appear on the 2D panel.
And at the same time, the buttonhole pattern will appear in 3D.
In the 3D tool bar,
use the move buttonhole tool.
Right-click on the buttonhole in the 2D window.
Right-click on the buttonhole.
In the pop-up menu,
select the buttonhole to be supported on the symmetrical panel.
In the 3D window, select the buttonhole tool.
Right-click on the buttonhole in the 2D window.
Select the buttonhole in the 2D window.
Right-click to align them.
Left-click on the buttonhole.
Draw the seam allowances and the tassel on the embroidered
many times
Use the 17 button toJaing the button and the button
sign, use it to select the function to move the button
with all pointing looked in the
above check icon
button on the Embmin box
your rightus click
select the photocopy bubble bar
from one click select
copy to the IS cev Entrade
Adjust the angle of the buckle in the shape editor
Use the same method to add buckles and buckles on the collar
And tighten them
In the 3D tool bar, select the move tool and select the center collar
Adjust the angle in the shape editor
Fold the front and center collar
Right click on the menu and select the direction to be turned
So that the buckle is outside
Select the buckle in the shape editor
Adjust the angle in the shape editor
The opening and closing points
Right click on the menu and select the direction to be turned
So that the buckle is outside
In the 2D window, use the edit tool
Select the bottom line and right click on the menu
Select the menu in the menu
The inner line is the border
In the dialogue box, enter the distance and click OK
In the 3D tool bar, select the fold arrangement tool
On the 3D costume
On the 3D costume, click on the newly created inner line
Will display the fold arrangement positioning tool
According to the arrow, only the fold 10
In order to fold the fold 10 more accurately
Need to set the fold angle for the inner line
Select the edit sheet tool in the 2D tool bar
Select the fold line on the 2D version
Set the angle of the fold line to 360 degrees
Activate the simulation
When the 3D costume is fully scrolled
Click again to close the simulation
Select the buckle in the object window
In the attribute editor
You can change the shape and size of the buckle
Also change the color of the buckle
In the attribute editor, select the buckle
Click on the button to close the eyes
In the attribute editor, you can adjust the shape and size of the buckle
From the 2D costume window
Double click to open the F & F file
Open the POS folder, double-click to open the FV203 file, or drag it into the 3D window.
In the dialog box, click OK.
Change the model position to a vertical position.
Choose the fabric in the Fabric folder in the library window.
Press and hold the left button on the fabric to drag it into the Fabric 1 in the object window.
Activate the simulation, so that the fabric can be used in 3D clothing.
In the object window, click on the fabric, and change the color of the fabric.
In the 3D tool bar, select the tool to increase the quality of the clothing.
In the dialog box, click OK.
Activate the simulation, so that the setting can be used in 3D clothing.
Include the arms and legs of the model.
Activate the simulation, so that the model can be used in 3D clothing.
And in the window that's not in the Fabric 1, we get into the model.
Click on the model that we just created.
And in the default choice, click on the model.